financenewstalk.com 2019-03-02

# Privacy | A Financial Inform Ation Release Platform

#### You are welcome to visit and use http://financenewstalk.com/ in this privacy notice we declare to the visitor’s privacy promise.Without you agree, we will never put your personal data provided to any third person has nothing to do with this web site service.  
If you access this web site, you accept this privacy statement.The following text I stand for information collection and use of public.This website’s privacy statement will continue to improve, with the increase of standing service, we will update our privacy statement.  
You are always welcome to view this statement, and feedback to us your opinion 

1.the special attention of minors  
If you are under 18, you have no right to use the service, so we hope you will not provide any personal information to us.If you are under 18, you can only be accompanied by a parent or guardian to use the service.

2.What information we collect you?  
This website USES Cookies to collect information about how visitors use the site (see the use of Cookies), in some parts of this web site, we will ask you for specific information (see online form and job applicants).In addition, you do not need to provide your information to the use of this web site.

3.Your trading behavior  
We track the IP address for the truthfulness of the identity and transaction identification, safety and other meet the requirements of the state.If we didn’t find any security issues, we will delete after 60 days we collected by the IP address.We also tracks throughout the page to access the data.Throughout the page to access the data are used to reflect the traffic, so that we can make plans for future growth (for example, increase the server).  
Because of your trading activity and other data, we will use these statistics to membership classification, so that targeted to provide new services to our members and opportunities.We’ll let you know by your email address to the new services and opportunities.

4.The use of cookies  
Cookies are small amounts of data, in case you do not refuse to accept cookies, cookies will be sent to your browser, and stored in your computer’s hard drive.We use cookies to the data store you visit our website, when you access or visit our website again, we can identify your identity, and through the analysis of data provide more better service for you.  
You have the right to accept or refuse to accept cookies.You can change the browser Settings to refuse to accept cookies, but we need to remind you, because you refuse to accept cookies, you might not be able to use depends on the part of cookies on our website.

5.Information disclosure  
We will not provide to any third party, sell, rent, share and transaction user’s personal information.When in the following cases, the user’s personal information will be goodwill disclosure of some or all of:  
1, subject to consent by the user, disclosed to a third party;  
2, such as user is eligible complainants of intellectual property and has filed a complaint, should be the complainant demands, to be the complainant disclosure, in order to both sides  
Possible rights disputes;  
3, according to the relevant provisions of the laws, or administrative or judicial body, disclosed to third parties or administrative, judicial institutions;  
4, if users in violation of the relevant Chinese law or policy, need to be disclosed to a third party;  
5, to provide you with the required products and services, and the user’s personal information must be Shared with third parties;  
6, other site according to the law or the website policy think proper disclosure.

6\. Links to Other Sites  
Our Site may contain links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.

7\. Commitment  
We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Seeking Alpha’s Sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.

8\. Your Consent  
By using this Site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to Seeking Alpha’s processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.
